<Page>
    <PageNavBar label="Project Settings" />

    <PageContent>
        <Box
            display="flex"
            flexDirection="column"
            gap="2"
            sx:mb="200px"
            sx:mt="1em"
            sx:width="100%"
            sx:maxWidth="1000px"
            sx:mx="auto"
        >
            <Markdown>
                Welcome to the Project Settings page! This is where you configure the fundamentals that shape your workspace, collaboration model, and project identity.

                ---

                ### 🏷️ Project Metadata

                Your project settings define the core identity of this workspace:

                - **Name**: Display name across the UI  
                - **Identifier**: Internal slug used in URLs or integration references  
                - **Created On**: Timestamp for project creation  
                - **Owner**: Primary admin or organizational owner  

                Keeping this metadata accurate ensures traceability and helps external integrations align with your naming conventions.

                ---

                ### 🔐 Permissions & Roles

                Settings here help define **who can do what**:

                - Invite new collaborators  
                - Promote/demote users (e.g., Admin, Editor, Viewer)  
                - Set up access tiers (e.g., only Admins can edit Gantt charts)  
                - Manage sensitive data or security-critical areas  

                Good permission hygiene ensures accountability without friction.

                ---

                ### 🛠️ Configuration Areas

                This space may eventually allow you to modify or define:

                - Default view (Board, Gantt, Wiki, etc.)  
                - Project-wide tags and labels  
                - Preferred date format and timezone  
                - Enable/disable experimental features  

                These settings streamline the experience for every contributor.

                ---

                ### 🔁 Project Lifecycle Management

                You’ll be able to define:

                - **Start & end dates** for the project  
                - **Phases or milestones** (e.g., Planning, Execution, Delivery)  
                - Rules for archiving completed tasks or freezing old issues  

                Project settings give structure to the lifespan of work—not just the tasks within it.

                ---

                ### 🌐 Integrations & Webhooks

                This section may include:

                - API keys or OAuth settings  
                - Integration toggles (Slack, GitHub, etc.)  
                - Webhooks for triggering automations on status change or issue creation  

                Settings here allow your project to **extend beyond this UI** into your broader tooling ecosystem.

                ---

                ### 🧹 Danger Zone

                Some actions are sensitive and irreversible:

                - **Delete Project**  
                - **Transfer Ownership**  
                - **Purge All Data**

                These options, when implemented, will be gated with confirmations and limited to Admin roles only.

                ---

                ### 📌 Final Notes

                Project settings are the foundation layer. Think of them as your project’s DNA: they don't change often, but when they do, they shape everything downstream.

                More configuration options will be added over time as your needs grow.
            </Markdown>

        </Box>
    </PageContent>
</Page>